<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on Quality Bytes GmbH</title><link>https://qualitybytes.de/en/</link><description>Recent content in Home on Quality Bytes GmbH</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>de-de</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 12:58:02 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://qualitybytes.de/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Creating users in Azure SQL DB</title><link>https://qualitybytes.de/en/blog/benutzer-in-azure-sql-db-anlegen/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://qualitybytes.de/en/blog/benutzer-in-azure-sql-db-anlegen/</guid><description>After creating a database under Microsoft Azure, the next step is usually to create a user who is to be authorized in the corresponding database.
Unfortunately, there is currently no direct option for this in the web interface of the Azure portal. Only the admin user for the DB server can be configured there. For security reasons, however, this should not be the user with which you later access the database from your own application.</description></item><item><title>Reinforcement as Software Developer .NET, Frontend Developer Angular, Xamarin Developer or ASP.NET Core Developer wanted</title><link>https://qualitybytes.de/en/blog/verstaerkung-bei-der-quality-bytes-gmbh-in-sinzig-gesucht-softwareentwickler-dotnet-softwareentwickler-angular-xamarin-asp-dotnet-core/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 08:58:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://qualitybytes.de/en/blog/verstaerkung-bei-der-quality-bytes-gmbh-in-sinzig-gesucht-softwareentwickler-dotnet-softwareentwickler-angular-xamarin-asp-dotnet-core/</guid><description>This might be your new desk For our team in Sinzig at the Rhine, between Bonn and Koblenz, we are looking for several software developers with immediate effect. We develop exciting customer solutions in the web and mobile environment in a team of four developers.
In doing so, we rely on modern technologies, tools, and approaches, such as
ASP.NET Core Angular Xamarin Azure DevOps git Unit Testing Typescript C# We currently have various positions available.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://qualitybytes.de/en/contact/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 11:54:28 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://qualitybytes.de/en/contact/</guid><description>Feel free to contact us if you have any questions.</description></item><item><title>Disclaimer</title><link>https://qualitybytes.de/en/disclaimer/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 11:54:28 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://qualitybytes.de/en/disclaimer/</guid><description>Liability and Intellectual Property Rights Information Liability Disclaimer While the content of this website has been put together with great care and reflects our current knowledge, it is provided for information purposes without being legally binding, unless the disclosure of this information is required by law (e.g. the legal information), the privacy policy, terms and conditions or mandatory instructions for consumers). We reserve the right to modify or delete the content, whether in full or in part, provided this does not affect our existing contractual obligations.</description></item><item><title>Document Generation</title><link>https://qualitybytes.de/en/software/document-creation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 11:54:28 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://qualitybytes.de/en/software/document-creation/</guid><description>Every day, countless documents are created in offices. Contracts, invoices, quotations, status reports, vacation requests, travel requests, labels, attendance certificates, or name badges are just a few examples.
Most such documents are probably created manually. So, an employee copies an old file, replaces (hopefully) all variable components of the document with the new values, saves the file, possibly exports it as a PDF, and prints it.
It is obvious that this process is not only very time-consuming, but above all error-prone.</description></item><item><title>Imprint</title><link>https://qualitybytes.de/en/imprint/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 11:54:28 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://qualitybytes.de/en/imprint/</guid><description>Legal Notice Provider Quality Bytes GmbH
Brunnenstraße 21
53498 Bad Breisig
Germany
Contact Options E-Mail Address: info@qualitybytes.de
Phone: +49 2633 48 99 430
Representatives Representative/s: André Krämer (CEO)
Journalistic-Editorial Services Responsible for content: André Krämer
Audiovisual Media Services Country of domicile: Germany
Competent regulatory or supervisory authority: State Media Authority of Rhineland-Palatinate, https://www.lmk-online.de/
Company Details VAT identification number: DE319550948
Professional Liability Insurance HISCOX SA
Arnulfstraße 31
80636 Munich
Germany
Register, Type of Register and Register Number Commercial Register The register is administered by: Register Court Koblenz Register number: HRB 26354</description></item><item><title>Mobile Apps</title><link>https://qualitybytes.de/en/software/mobile/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 11:54:28 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://qualitybytes.de/en/software/mobile/</guid><description>Transforming business processes to mobile devices can be a productivity boon for companies of all sizes. However, it is not enough to simply equip employees with mobile devices, i.e. smartphones and tablets, or to introduce a &amp;ldquo;bring your own device&amp;rdquo; (BYOD) strategy. It also requires specialized business apps, so-called enterprise mobile apps, which map the actual business process on a mobile basis.
We at Quality Bytes GmbH have specialized in the development of mobile business applications for Android, iOS, and Windows.</description></item><item><title>Privacy</title><link>https://qualitybytes.de/en/privacy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 11:54:28 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://qualitybytes.de/en/privacy/</guid><description>As of 21. January 2022
Privacy Policy Preamble With the following privacy policy, we would like to inform you which types of your personal data (hereinafter also abbreviated as &amp;ldquo;data&amp;rdquo;) we process for which purposes and in which scope. The privacy statement applies to all processing of personal data carried out by us, both in the context of providing our services and in particular on our websites, in mobile applications, and within external online presences, such as our social media profiles (hereinafter collectively referred to as &amp;ldquo;online services&amp;rdquo;).</description></item><item><title>Team</title><link>https://qualitybytes.de/en/about/team/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 11:54:28 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://qualitybytes.de/en/about/team/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Web Apps</title><link>https://qualitybytes.de/en/software/web/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 11:54:28 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://qualitybytes.de/en/software/web/</guid><description>When implementing websites and web applications, we have specialized in the Microsoft platform. In these projects, we work primarily with ASP.NET MVC and the ASP.NET Web API or ASP.NET Core. On the client, we use Angular.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://qualitybytes.de/en/jobgruende/jobgruende/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://qualitybytes.de/en/jobgruende/jobgruende/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>