<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Software on Quality Bytes GmbH</title><link>https://qualitybytes.de/en/software/</link><description>Recent content in Software on Quality Bytes GmbH</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>de-de</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 12:58:02 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://qualitybytes.de/en/software/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Document Generation</title><link>https://qualitybytes.de/en/software/document-creation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 11:54:28 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://qualitybytes.de/en/software/document-creation/</guid><description>Every day, countless documents are created in offices. Contracts, invoices, quotations, status reports, vacation requests, travel requests, labels, attendance certificates, or name badges are just a few examples.
Most such documents are probably created manually. So, an employee copies an old file, replaces (hopefully) all variable components of the document with the new values, saves the file, possibly exports it as a PDF, and prints it.
It is obvious that this process is not only very time-consuming, but above all error-prone.</description></item><item><title>Mobile Apps</title><link>https://qualitybytes.de/en/software/mobile/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 11:54:28 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://qualitybytes.de/en/software/mobile/</guid><description>Transforming business processes to mobile devices can be a productivity boon for companies of all sizes. However, it is not enough to simply equip employees with mobile devices, i.e. smartphones and tablets, or to introduce a &amp;ldquo;bring your own device&amp;rdquo; (BYOD) strategy. It also requires specialized business apps, so-called enterprise mobile apps, which map the actual business process on a mobile basis.
We at Quality Bytes GmbH have specialized in the development of mobile business applications for Android, iOS, and Windows.</description></item><item><title>Web Apps</title><link>https://qualitybytes.de/en/software/web/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 11:54:28 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://qualitybytes.de/en/software/web/</guid><description>When implementing websites and web applications, we have specialized in the Microsoft platform. In these projects, we work primarily with ASP.NET MVC and the ASP.NET Web API or ASP.NET Core. On the client, we use Angular.</description></item></channel></rss>